twilighted.net 2018-12-21

# Twilighted :: All-Inclusive, High-Quality Twilight Fan Fiction

Privacy Policy

Twilighted.net respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us. Any personal information you provide to Twilighted.net will be known only to two parties: you and the staff of Twilighted.net. Your username (penname) will be available to other members for purposes of community participation. However, we will not disclose the fact of your membership by username, except in specific situations such as to law enforcement agencies as specified in this document. 

The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our site and its features. 

**Announcements and spam**

From time to time, members may receive notification of new services, changes to policies, etc. We will not send you other email at the address you provide, except for infrequent communications to resolve issues that may arise with your own Twilighted.net account. 

We will not sell, rent or give your email address to any third party. You are free at any time to substitute an alternate e-mail address if you wish to keep the one you initially registered private. 

**Use of cookies at Twilighted.net**

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored in your computer's memory or written on your computer's hard drive. 

We do not use cookies to track usage on our site. 

**Participants**

Twilighted.net members are expected to comply with our Terms of Service, but we cannot control third parties' use of information you may choose to provide via Twilighted.net forums or your user home page, nor can we vouch for the integrity of the participants you may communicate with, including but not limited to participants in forums, etc. Sharing information with other Twilighted.net members is a matter of individual choice and judgement. If you choose to take part in any Twilighted.net forum, etc, whatever you may disclose in that discussion area is made known to others who may read the forum. 

**Other disclosure of personal information**

Twilighted.net will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, or (ii) as required by law. Any subscriber whose information is sought in accordance with this policy will be advised of the inquiry as soon as practical. Notification of such inquiries will be emailed to members before disclosures are made, unless notification is prohibited by law. 

This privacy policy may not protect information you voluntarily disclose to others via a post to any online conference, email list, chat or send tool or any other communication environment within or from our service. 

**Cancellation and data removal policies**

If you would like to end your membership and to delete any data, you can close your account and request data removal from [helpdesk@twilighted.net](mailto:helpdesk@twilighted.net). If you wish to delete any of your own posts before ending your membership you may do so. 

**For further information; contacts**

If you have any further questions or concerns about Twilighted.net's privacy policies and use of personal information, please send them to [helpdesk@twilighted.net](mailto:helpdesk@twilighted.net). 

| 

* * *

© 2008, 2009 Twilighted Enterprises, LLC. All Rights Reserved.  
Unauthorized duplication is a violation of applicable laws.  
 **Privacy Policy** | **Terms of Service**

All publicly recognizable characters, settings, etc[.](http://stroybat.org/) are the intellectual property of their respective owners. The original characters and plot are the property of Stephenie Meyer. No copyright infringement is intended.
